I've been around $2.8 million in just
trading in 2024 and I know this might
sound crazy but in this video I'm going
to show you the exact strategy that I
use in order to make $2.8 million day
trading in 2024 and I didn't make this
video about me like at all I made this
video about you guys because I want you
to learn from my mistakes and you can
use the exact points that I learned in
this year so you can go ahead and add
these profits into your trading career
in 2024 and that's because I've made
more than $2.8 million in this year with
this trading strategy and I'm going to
show you everything in this video so you
can make more money but only if you
follow every single step picture the
strategy as an engine of a car the
engine won't work with every single
function of the engine working if you're
missing just one thing or just a little
electrical issue the engine won't work
same thing with the Martin so you don't
have the right strategy and just one
thing is missing you simply will not
succeed so make sure you watch the video
all the way to the end so you can get
every single step in order to succeed
this year with this strategy so let's
get into the video that takes me to the
first point which is going to be the
less money you risk the more trades you
take and the less trades you take the
more money you make let me explain that
in just a second the less money you risk
you feel as if you have to trade more in
order to make more money simply because
you feel that the more you work in the
markets the more the more money you're
going to make because you have smaller
amounts of money so the more you put in
the more you should make and that is
actually completely wrong that is not
how the markets work at all you can't
picture the markets as if it were to be
a job like oh just because I'm making
$20 an hour I have to work more hours in
order to make more money just because
you're betting $ 20 $30 on a trade does
it mean that you have to bet more trades
in order to make money now obviously the
answer the short answer to that would be
yes obviously it's logical but that
doesn't mean that you're going to be
profitable or make a lot of money in the
long run by taking more trades with a
little bit of money that's not how you
get rich and nonetheless stay Rich this
is what beginner Traders create as a
habit thinking that they're going to
become successful like this over time
and it is one of the biggest mistakes
that you can possibly be ever making
because in order for you to actually
become successful in the market so for
to actually make money you have to take
less trades risking a lot more money
that's how you get rich and stay Rich
because you're focusing more on the
actual quality of the trade not of how
many types of Trades you would take
you're taking trades that actually make
more sense than taking 10 trades a day
versus one trade a day I can guarantee
you that one trade that you patiently
wait for and it aligns with everything
in your strategy it's going to make you
more money than simply firing at a bunch
of different traits picture yourself in
the market as if you were to be a sniper
every single single shot counts
everything that you take is precise and
perfectly calculated you don't want to
just be shooting like a machine gun at a
bunch of things and hoping something
hits and trust me I definitely
understand this personally myself
because when I started trading about 6
and 1 half years ago I was taking trades
with $50 $100 and I was thinking that
okay if I bet $50 every single time and
I take five trades a day I'm going to
make more money every single time and
that's not how it works because the more
you trade is not the more you make like
the beginning mindset and it's actually
a very poor mindset to have because it's
going to affect your results down the
road actually statistically and
emotionally because you're going to be
more drain because you're taking more
Trad you're just going to be more
exhausted because you're doing a lot
more and having a lot less results and
the moment that I actually figured this
out was when the moment that I would not
take any trades I would realize that the
trades that I would have taken the
market actually went against what I was
predicting and this kind of made me sit
back and be like well if I do this more
often and I only focus on trades that
make sense I'm avoiding a lot of those
losses that I would normally be taking
and I'm only focusing on the wins so
that instead of me taking five to six
trades a day I was taking maybe two or
three which is still on the high end and
as time went on I started realizing the
less I do in the market the more I
actually make because when I actually
get involved I'm risking a lot more
money because this trade simply makes a
lot more sense for example about two
months ago about a month and a half ago
I was literally without taking one
single trade for 3 weeks 3 weeks without
doing anything in the markets literally
just watching it and waiting for a trade
setup to appear and don't get me wrong
within those 3 weeks some nice trade
setups appeared but I I asked myself I'm
like do I want to be the guy that just
takes any trade or do I want to take the
trade and about 3 or 4 days after
waiting for 3 weeks I actually broke my
record for the biggest trade that I've
ever had and that was
$360,000 in one single trade and that is
because I was patient I was extremely
patient waiting for that one trade that
goes back to the original point which is
the less trades you take the more money
you make and this is literally just the
rule this is coming from a successful
and profitable Trader and I encourage
this to my Traders every single day
picture yourself as if every single
trade you would take in your whole
entire life would be in a punch card you
would only have access to 20 trades in
your whole entire trading career I can
guarantee you you're going to be
extremely selective about every single
trade that you take because you only
have 20 tries in your whole entire
career and the odds of you making money
within those 20 trades in your whole
entire lifespan it's going to be a lot
higher if you were to have unlimited
amount of Trades why because you're
taking the trades that make sense and
avoiding the ones that don't so step one
less trades equals more money if you got
this which is the most important Point
drop a comment below and let me know
because this is extremely important to
me I keep making these videos out there
for you guys and because of that not
every day is a trading day that's
actually the next point which is point
two that I'm going to be talking about
in this video let's say as if you were
to be a surfer your job is to go out
there into the ocean and surf these
waves and every single time you catch a
wave you make money pretty cool
lifestyle right I would love to be a
surfer I've never surfed in my life but
would be fun so let's say your job as a
surfer is to go out there and Surf and
there's some days that you go out there
to the beach and there's no wind there's
no wind there's no waves there's no
waves you can't surf you can't surf you
don't make money what are you going to
do about it nothing you can't do
anything if the ocean doesn't give you
the resources and the ability to go surf
but that doesn't make you not a surfer
that doesn't mean that you're now not a
surfer that just simply means that
there's no opportunity for you to go out
there and make money as a surfer surfing
the waves because the ocean is not
giving you the needs in order for you to
do that well it's the exact same thing
in the markets not every single day is a
trading day and simply because you don't
trade that doesn't mean that you're not
a Trader just means that there's no
opportunities out there for you to trade
your job as a Trader is to come into the
market sit down in front the computer
and wait for a good trading setup to
appear if the market doesn't give you
the momentum if the market doesn't give
you the analysis entry if the market
doesn't give you a trading plan you
simply don't take a trade you just can't
make something out of nothing for
example the surfer when they were to
head out to the ocean as they're getting
to the ocean they look up at the palm
trees they would see that the trees
aren't moving which would mean that
there is no waves that are going to
potentially be created but you don't
ever know for sure so you actually want
to get to the beach so you can see for
yourself more into detail what you're
actually executing on if it's going to
be giving you the entry in order for you
to enter the W and then when you get to
the beach you can see that there's no
wind it's a cloudy day there's no waves
you do not enter the wave cuz if you go
out there you're just going to Simply
waste your time same thing when I come
into the markets every single time I go
to the markets first thing I do every
single morning is I sit down and I look
at the volume so the market moves in
different sessions so for example you
have New York session which is going to
be the session of New York where it
moves for about 5 6 hours it's where the
stock exchange opens and all of the US
money is being moved then shortly after
that you have Asia and Tokyo session
which is pretty much the slow moving
sessions which you would have obviously
the Tokyo and then the Asia money being
moved around which creates that type of
liquidity into the market but sometimes
it's not as effective as New York and
then you have London session which is
one of the highest moving sessions in
the whole entire Market this is the
session that is going to let you know
what happens in the Europe London which
moves the majority of the market outside
of the US so every single morning when I
come into New York session to trade that
means that London session has just
passed over because London session where
I'm based right now in Miami Florida
happens at around 3:00 in the morning
all the way up to about 6:00 7 in the
morning so there's that overnight
session that I would see in the morning
when I go trade and when if I go trade
in the morning I see that the overnight
session didn't have any momentum that
pretty much is going to determine to me
that that New York session is not going
to have a lot of momentum which simply
takes me to The Next Step it's actually
looking at the size of the candlesticks
because I'm trading on candlesticks so I
want to see if the candlesticks are big
or are they small if they're small I
simply am not interested in entering the
market because it just does not make any
sense there is no momentum in the market
you see this by looking at the session
and you can see the momentum roll over
and if those two simple things do not
check out I do not take a trade and that
makes that day non-trading day and
because I don't take a trade doesn't
mean that I'm not a Trader same thing as
a surfer you go out there there's no
wind there's no waves you can't do
anything about it you simply do not surf
for the day so not every day is going to
be a trading day and the day that you do
actually enter a trade and you do
actually win you never want to celebrate
a win before it hits your take profit
and that leads me to my third point
which is never celebrate a win before
you close your trade now I know this
might be a little bit of a funny one but
it's actually extremely true you I can't
tell you how many times this year I have
executed a trade it's gone about 25%
into profit and I already start flexing
on Instagram or I start feeling as if I
were to win the trade already and little
do I know that 1 hour later the whole
entire trade reverses so I felt like the
and when the trade was about 25% into my
profit and I was already celebrating as
if the trade would have hit my whole
entire takeprofit that's not how this
goes you only celebrate a win when your
win is hit to the end why because what
this is it just creates an influx of
emotion and it just throws off your
whole entire trading psychology if
you're celebrating your trade a little
bit too early which obviously you never
want to do so this actually happened to
me earlier this year where I was going
about to get my my first biggest trading
week for the year and I remember that I
was about 30 to five to like 40% into my
takeprofit and I said that's it it's a
winner I know it's going to win and I
took a nap when I woke up from the nap
trade ah hit my stop loss and this was
probably the most humilating thing that
can happen because everything that I do
when I post on Instagram is literally
what's happening live into the markets
and you could I just share it out there
with you guys and you know people were
like trolling me in the DMS and stuff so
yeah never celebrate your wins before it
actually hits you take profit and if you
were to actually ever do this and you
celebrate before your trade actually
hits your take profit and then it goes
into stop loss you don't ever want to
change anything from your trading plan
that is my next fourth point which is
nothing ever changes in your trading
plan doesn't matter if you win a trade
doesn't matter if you lose a trade
doesn't matter if you're breaking it
doesn't matter your trading plan should
never change and if you're this far into
the video make sure you hit that
subscribe button because I'm going to be
sharing with you my trading plan in just
a second and why would you not want to
be subscribed to the person that's going
to share the trading plan hit the
Subscribe button and I say that you
never want to change anything about your
trading plan it's because well first of
all in the first place you should only
ever create your trading plan on the
weekend or whenever the market is closed
because you don't want to create a
trading plan while you're warmed up and
you're in the scene and you're in the
moment you want to Cate you want to
create a trading plan when you're cold
cold- minded and even if you wanted to
execute a trade you simply can't like
let's say you want to trade a trading
plan on Saturday the Market's closed on
Saturday you can't do anything about it
so what does that make you do it makes
you think more about the trading plan
that you're actually creating gets you
into more detail about it and make you
ask the question does this trading plan
even [__] make sense because some of
you guys be creating the most random
rules I don't even know where you guys
get it from and it might just be a
oneoff trade or it might be a twoof
trade but it's not a statistically
proven over 10 course of Trades that
you're going to make money so this is
the key when it comes to the trading
plan that no matter what happens in the
scenario of you Crea creting it when
you're on a cold mindset which is the
only time you should ever create it
whenever you're in the hot mindset
you're in the hot chair you're in the
market you're involved and something
just simply didn't work out because no
trading plan is ever 100% win rate and
you lose a trade don't change anything
if you want to Revenge trade and get
back into another trade the next minute
the next hour or the next day don't ever
change anything of something that
already works all you're doing is
digging yourself into a bigger hole and
then now you've created a new trading
plan or adjusted it when you're on a
warm mindset and then when you go
compared to the one that you created on
the cold mindset it just doesn't check
out and now you're just all over the
place and you might just even end up
giving up on trading because it might
seem very overwhelming so pick one
trading plan and stick to it give it the
chance to play out I can guarantee you
many of these trading plans and
strategies out there work you guys just
don't give it the chance to play out cuz
think about it the market is going to do
two two things literally I haven't
figured out what else it's going to do
it's either going to go up or it's going
to go down it's a 50/50 win rate 100%
all you have to do is just find the way
for it to make more sense to go up with
it or find the way that make it make
sense to go down with it that is
literally it and if you give it the
course of 10 different attempts doing
the same exact thing every single time
and you have a positive risk reward I
can guarantee you you will make money
and I will put my my name behind that I
will put anything behind that it just
simply makes sense and as I promised you
guys I'm going to share with you my
trading plan but not in this video in
this video right here that you guys can
see I did a whole entire video dedicated
solely to my trading plan so you guys
can learn from it it's a step-by-step
trading plan that I personally use every
single day in addition to what I'm going
to share with you inside of this video
so if you want to see more of the
technical stuff make sure you guys go
watch this video right here and even
with that trading plan and with every
guidance not everybody can be a day
trader or not everybody can be a Trader
that leads me to my next point which is
not everybody is meant to be a
profitable Trader it's the simple harsh
truth I know it might hurt but I'm just
being honest I'm just saving some of you
guys some time and honestly like this
[__] you got to be built for it if
you're not if you don't have that dog in
you if you don't have that consistency
in you and you're going to show up every
single day without complaining if you're
not going to put all the excuses behind
you if you're not GNA make yourself a
100% dedicated person to the craft if
you're going to make no excuses this is
not for you this is easily extremely
accessible takes no actual physical work
and anybody can get involved but it is
not for everybody in order to get to
that next level now you can make a
little bit of money and you can
definitely get by by making a couple
thousand a month but if you really want
to hit home and be an extremely
successful Trader you have to determine
whether you are built for that or not
I'm telling you right now not everybody
is meant to be a Trader and the simplest
analogy that I can make is that
everybody can kick a soccer ball I can
kick a soccer ball you can kick a soccer
ball doesn't matter if you're overweight
doesn't matter if you're underweight
doesn't matter if you're athletic
doesn't matter if you're not athletic
doesn't matter anybody can kick a ball
into a big net it's very easy but not
everybody can be a professional soccer
player that taks extreme dedication
Health Energy Focus like it's not meant
for everybody to be a professional
soccer player even though the team has a
100 different types of players it's the
entry barrier is a lot easier than it
say compared to basketball which is a
lot smaller but not everybody can do it
professionally you know you can go to a
local park and you can play a little bit
and you know win but if you really want
to get to the big leagues it takes a lot
of dedication and time it's the same
exact thing with trading anybody can
click a buy or a sell button but not
everybody can do it over the time and
have the right mindset and the approach
to do it extremely success for for the
rest of their lives and I say this from
my personal experience I didn't know I
was going to be a Trader at the
beginning of my journey or even before
when I knew about trading I just knew I
was going to be successful but I didn't
KN exactly well I just knew that I had
that dog in me I had that consistency I
had that persistency I don't make
excuses I was going to give it my 100%
every single day no matter what I was
going to dial in to whatever I did and I
knew it was going to succeed I didn't
know it was going to be trading I just
knew that I had the willpower to put in
the work into something regardless
what's the outcome or what the struggle
was going to be that's exactly what set
and forget is all about and I'm not sure
this is your first time hearing set and
forget but if you want to know what set
and forget is click the link in the
description below because it literally
lets anybody that has that power in them
that consistency to make anywhere from
,000 to $11,500 a week as a beginner
Trader I literally show you the skills
that I use every single week in the
markets in order to get my students to
make anywhere from a th000 to $1,500 a
week as a beginner set or forget Trader
and personally myself I get on a call
every single Sunday with my students to
share my actual trading ideas so you
guys can literally copy me in what I do
every single week imagine having a coach
and him go with you to go play at a game
every single day the odds of you winning
that game are probably going to be very
high that's what I do with my students
every single weekend so if you want to
know more about what set and forget is
and see if trading is meant for you
simply click the video in the link below
which explains to you what set and
forget is all about it's a free video so
I appreciate you guys watching this
video all the way to the end if you are
not subscribed hit the Subscribe button
you guys are missing out on videos like
this every single week and I appreciate
you guys watching this video out way to
the end see you guys in the next video